Good afternoon! Thank you for calling XYZ Telecommunications. My name is Lisa. How can I assist you today?
Hi there! I'd like to update my contact information. I recently changed my phone number.
Of course! I'd be happy to help with that. First, for security purposes, may I please have your account number or service ID?
Sure, it's 123456.
Thank you. To further verify your identity, could you please confirm your date of birth and address?
My date of birth is January 15, 1985, and my address is 456 Elm Street, Springfield.
Perfect. Thank you for confirming that. Now, could you provide me with your new phone number?
It's 555-123-4567.
Got it. I'll update that information for you right away. Just a moment, please... All set! Your new phone number has been updated. Is there anything else I can help you with today?
No, that's all. Thank you so much!
You're welcome! A confirmation email with the changes has been sent to you. If you need any further assistance, feel free to call us anytime. Have a wonderful day!
Thanks, you too!