Thank you for calling XYZ Telecom. My name is Lisa. How can I assist you today?
Hi Lisa! My name is John, and I hope you’re having a great day. I was just looking at my bill and noticed a charge I didn't expect. Could you help me out with that?
Hi John! I'm doing well, thank you for asking. I'd be happy to help you with your bill. Can I please have your account number or service ID?
Sure, it’s 123456.
Thank you, John. Let me pull up your account. While I do that, could you tell me which charge you’re referring to?
It's a $15 charge listed as "additional services" on my latest statement.
I see the charge you're talking about. Let me explain that for you. This charge is for an international call you made last month. Does that ring a bell?
Oh, yes, I remember now! Thanks for clearing that up, Lisa.
No problem at all, John. Is there anything else I can help you with today?
Nope, that’s all. You’ve been great. Thanks again!
My pleasure, John. Have a wonderful day!