Good morning, you’ve reached XYZ Telecom. My name is Lisa. How can I assist you today?
I’ve been trying to set up new internet service for days, and I keep getting the runaround!
I’m really sorry to hear that, and I can understand how frustrating that must be. Let’s get this sorted out for you right away. May I have your name and contact information, please?
It’s Jane Smith, 555-987-6543.
Thank you, Jane. And what is the address where you’d like to set up the new service?
456 Oak Avenue.
Got it. Can you tell me a little more about the services you’re looking for? Are you interested in internet, phone, TV, or a combination?
Just internet, and I need it fast!
Absolutely, Jane. We have several high-speed internet plans available. Let me check if we can provide service to your address.
Fine.
I’ve confirmed that we can offer high-speed internet at 456 Oak Avenue. We have a plan offering speeds up to 500 Mbps for $50 per month. Would that work for you?
Yes, that’s fine. Just get it done.
Understood. I’ll process your order now. Do you need any additional equipment, or are you all set?
I have everything I need. Just get someone out here to install it.
I’ll schedule the earliest available installation appointment. How does tomorrow between 2 PM and 4 PM sound?
Finally! That works.
Great, Jane. Your installation is scheduled for tomorrow between 2 PM and 4 PM. You’ll receive a confirmation email shortly. Is there anything else I can help you with?
No, just make sure they show up.
We’ll be there, Jane. Thank you for choosing XYZ Telecom, and I apologize for any inconvenience you’ve experienced. Have a better day!