Good morning! Thank you for calling our support center. My name is Lisa. How can I help you today?
Hi Lisa! My name is John and I’ve been having some trouble with my internet connection for the past few hours. Can you help me out?
Of course, John! I’m really sorry for the inconvenience. Let’s get this sorted out for you. Can I please have your account number or service ID to get started?
Sure, it’s 12345678.
Great, thank you. Can you describe the issue you’re experiencing? Are there any error messages?
The internet just keeps dropping every few minutes. No specific error messages though.
I see. How long has this been happening, John?
It started this morning.
Thanks for that information. Let me quickly check if there is a known outage in your area.
It looks like there aren’t any reported outages. Let’s try some troubleshooting steps. Can you first try restarting your modem and router?
Sure, one second.
Okay, I’ve restarted them.
Perfect. Are all the cables securely connected and undamaged?
Yes, everything looks fine.
Alright, let’s check the lights on your modem/router. Are they all on and stable?
Yes, they’re all on and stable.
Great! Can you check if other devices in your house are also experiencing connectivity issues?
Yes, they all seem to be having the same problem.
Thank you for checking that. Since the basic steps haven’t resolved the issue, I’ll perform remote diagnostics.
It appears there’s an issue on our end. I’ll escalate this to our technical team. Here’s your trouble ticket number, 987654321. We’ll work on resolving this and provide an update soon.
Thank you, Lisa. You’ve been really helpful!
My pleasure, John. We’ll get this fixed as soon as possible. Have a wonderful day!