Thank you for calling XYZ Telecommunications. My name is Lisa. How can I assist you today?
My internet has been down for hours! I’m really frustrated!
I’m truly sorry for the inconvenience, and I understand how frustrating that can be. Let’s work together to get this resolved as quickly as possible. Can I please have your name and account number?
It’s John, and my account number is 789012.
Thank you, John. I’ll also need a bit more information to help you better. How long has this issue been going on, and have you made any recent changes to your equipment or service plan?
It started this morning, and no, nothing’s changed.
I appreciate the information. Let’s start by checking if there are any known outages in your area. Please hold for a moment.  John, it seems there are no known outages. Let’s proceed with some troubleshooting steps. Could you please restart your modem and router?
I’ve done that already, and it didn’t help!
I understand your frustration. Let’s try checking the modem and router lights. Are they all on and green?
The power light is green, but the internet light is off.
Thank you for that information. It seems like there might be an issue with the connection. Can you please check if any cables are loose or damaged?
All cables seem fine.
I see. Let me run a remote diagnostic to get more details. Please hold for a moment.  John, our diagnostics indicate a possible issue with the line. I’ll need to escalate this to our technical team. I’ll create a trouble ticket and provide you with the ticket number.
Fine, just get it fixed.
Absolutely. Your ticket number is 345678, and the estimated resolution timeframe is within 24 hours. We’ll keep you updated. Is there anything else I can assist you with today?
No, that’s it.
Thank you for your patience, John. We’ll resolve this as soon as possible. Have a good day.