Good afternoon! Thank you for calling XYZ Telecommunications. My name is Lisa. How can I assist you today?
My TV service is down, and I’m really annoyed! It’s been like this for hours!
I’m very sorry for the inconvenience, and I understand how upsetting that can be. Let’s get this fixed for you. Can I please have your name and account number?
It’s John, and my account number is 654321.
Thank you, Lisa. I’ll need a bit more information to help you better. How long have you been experiencing this issue, and have you made any recent changes to your equipment or service plan?
It started this morning, and no, I haven’t changed anything.
I appreciate the details. Let’s start by ensuring both your TV and set-top box are powered on. Could you please check that for me?
Yes, they’re both on.
Great. Now, let’s try resetting your set-top box. I’ll guide you through the steps. Are you ready?
Yes, go ahead.
Please press and hold the reset button on your set-top box for 10 seconds, then release it. Let’s wait for it to reboot.
Okay, it’s rebooting.
Excellent. Once it’s back on, could you check if the issue persists?
It’s working now! Thank you so much, Lisa!
I’m glad we could get it sorted out! If you have any more issues, please don’t hesitate to reach out. Is there anything else I can assist you with today?
No, that’s all. Thanks again!
You’re very welcome, John! Have a wonderful day!