Good morning! Thank you for calling XYZ Telecom. My name is Lisa. How can I assist you today?
Hi! I’m interested in setting up a new internet and TV service at my home. Can you help me with that?
Absolutely, I'd be delighted to help you with that. May I please have your name and contact information to get started?
Sure, my name is John Doe, and my number is 555-123-4567.
Thank you, John. And what is the service address where you’d like to set up the new services?
It’s 123 Maple Street.
Great, thank you! Now, could you tell me a bit more about what you’re looking for in your internet and TV services? Do you have any specific requirements or preferences?
I’m looking for high-speed internet and a good selection of TV channels, especially sports channels.
Perfect, we have several plans that might be a great fit for you. For high-speed internet, we offer speeds up to 1 Gbps. For TV, we have a package that includes all the major sports channels. Let me check if these services are available at your address.
That sounds good!
Wonderful! I’ve checked, and both our high-speed internet and comprehensive TV package are available at your address. The internet plan costs $60 per month, and the TV package is $80 per month. Would you like to proceed with these options?
Yes, that works for me.
Excellent choice! I’ll process your order now. Could you please confirm if you need any additional equipment or if you’ll be porting your current phone number?
No additional equipment needed, and I don’t need to port a phone number.
Great! The next step is to schedule an installation appointment. When would be a convenient time for you?
How about this Friday?
Let me check... Yes, we have an opening this Friday between 10 AM and 12 PM. Does that work for you?
Yes, that’s perfect.
Fantastic! I’ve scheduled your installation for this Friday between 10 AM and 12 PM. You’ll receive a confirmation email shortly with all the details. Is there anything else I can assist you with today?
No, that’s all. Thank you so much!
You’re very welcome, John! Thank you for choosing XYZ Telecom. Have a great day!