Good morning, you’ve reached XYZ Telecom. My name is Lisa. How can I assist you today?
I’m really frustrated! I’ve been trying to get new TV service, and it’s been a nightmare!
I’m truly sorry to hear that. Let’s make sure we resolve this for you right away. May I have your name and contact information, please?
It’s Michael Johnson, 555-321-4321.
Thank you, Michael. And what is the address where you’d like to set up the new service?
789 Pine Street.
Thank you. Can you tell me more about what you’re looking for in your TV service? Any specific channels or packages?
I want a good selection of family channels and some movie channels. I’ve been trying to get this set up for over a week!
I understand your frustration, Michael, and I apologize for the delay. We have a family package that includes a wide variety of family and movie channels. Let me check if this is available at your address.
Please do.
Good news, Michael! Our family package is available at 789 Pine Street. It’s $70 per month and includes all the channels you’re looking for. Shall we proceed with this package?
Yes, that sounds good.
Great! I’ll process your order now. Do you need any additional equipment?
No, just the service.
Understood. Let’s get your installation scheduled. How does Thursday between 9 AM and 11 AM sound?
That works for me.
Excellent, Michael. Your installation is scheduled for Thursday between 9 AM and 11 AM. You’ll receive a confirmation email shortly. Is there anything else I can help you with today?
No, that’s all. Thank you for sorting this out.
You’re very welcome, Michael. I’m glad we could resolve this for you. Thank you for choosing [Company Name]. Have a great day!
Thanks, you too!
Thank you, Michael. Take care!