Good morning! Thank you for calling TeleLink Services. My name is Lisa. How can I assist you today?
Hi Lisa! I'm Jane. I hope you're having a great day. I'd like to upgrade my current plan. What are my options?
Hi Jane! Thank you for calling. I'm doing well, and I hope you are too. Let's get started. Can I please have your account number or service ID to pull up your details?
Sure, it's 123456.
Great, thank you. I see that you are on our Basic Plan. Could you tell me a bit more about what you're looking for in your new plan? Are you interested in more data, faster speeds, or additional services?
Mostly more data and maybe some premium channels.
Got it. We have a couple of options that might suit your needs. Our Premium Plan offers double the data you currently have and includes three premium channels for an additional $20 a month. Does that sound good to you?
That sounds perfect! What about the billing changes?
Your new plan will be prorated for this month, so you'll see a partial charge for the upgrade on your next bill. Moving forward, your monthly bill will reflect the new amount.
Awesome, let's do it!
Wonderful! I'll process that change for you right now. The upgrade will take effect within the next hour. You might need to restart your modem and TV box to see the new channels.
Thanks, Sarah. You've been very helpful.
My pleasure, Jane! I'll send you a confirmation email with all the details. Is there anything else I can assist you with today?
No, that's all. Have a great day!
You too, Jane. Thank you for choosing XYZ Telecom!