Good morning! Thank you for calling XYZ Telecommunications. My name is Lisa. How can I assist you today?
Hi Lisa! I'm having some trouble with my internet connection. It keeps cutting out.
Oh no, I'm sorry to hear that! Let's get this sorted out for you. May I have your name and account number to get started?
Sure, my name is Shawn, and my account number is 123456.
Thank you, Shawn. I’ll also need a bit more information to help you better. How long have you been experiencing this issue, and have you made any recent changes to your equipment or service plan?
It started yesterday, and no, I haven’t changed anything recently.
Got it. Let’s start with some basic troubleshooting steps. Could you please restart your modem and router? I'll hold the line while you do that.
Alright, give me a minute.  Okay, I’ve restarted them.
Great. Now, can you check if all the lights on the modem and router are on and green?
Yes, they are.
Perfect. Are you still experiencing the connectivity issue on all your devices?
No, it seems to be working fine now!
That’s wonderful to hear! If you encounter any more issues, don’t hesitate to call us back. Is there anything else I can help you with today?
Nope, that’s all. Thanks, Lisa!
You’re welcome, Shawn! Have a great day!